(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-10T22:24:04.894221",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
[もうどうなってもいいや / 星街すいせい]
[Title: I Don't Care What Happens Anymore / Hoshimachi Suisei]
堂々巡りのファンタジー
A fantasy going in circles...
あらすじなぞる謎々
tracing a storyline of riddles.
本能のままに鼓動が
My heartbeat, driven by pure instinct,
解き放つ衝動
releases this impulse.
oh... どうなってもいいや
Oh... I don't care what happens anymore.
他人に言われちゃったら知りたいだけ
I just want to know what others say about me,
不思議に願う本当の気持ち
my true feelings, wishing for something strange.
苦し紛れの言い訳は
An excuse made out of desperation
いらない 意味ない 君はどうなの？
is useless and meaningless. What about you?
期待を失ったみたいだ
It feels like I've lost all expectations,
どこにもあてのない旅へ
going on a journey with no destination...
同じことばかり繰り返して
Repeating the same things over and over again,
いつから裸足のままで踊る
since when did we start dancing barefoot?
誰かが作り繕う物語より
Rather than a story patched up by someone else,
消えないように 魔法みたいな
so it won't fade away, like magic...
もしも僕が主人公なら
If I were the protagonist,
最後はどうなってもハッピーエンド
in the end, no matter what, it must be a happy ending.
それなら好きにさせてよ
So let me do as I please.
もう どうなってもいいや
I don't care what happens anymore!
真っ逆さまに落ちていく
Falling headfirst down,
重力のない引力
drawn by a gravity-defying attraction.
君と僕が交わって とりこ
You and I cross paths, completely captivated.
一切合切持って行って
Take everything away,
残すことなく人生を謳歌
and enjoy this life to the absolute fullest.
交わり合う星に思いを馳せて
Letting my thoughts wander to the intersecting stars...
月が揺らいだら
And if the moon wavers,
なんてこの夜はすべて終わって行く
this entire night will come to an end...
もう どうなってもいいや
I don't care what happens anymore.
曖昧な言葉に
With ambiguous words,
揺れている君の瞳の奥へ
into the depths of your trembling eyes,
ピントを合わせてフォーカス
adjust the focus.
誰も触れたことのない真実のその先へ
Beyond the truth that no one has ever touched,
簡単にいかないからもっと
because it won't be easy, so give me more,
もっともっともっと遠くに
more, more, and even further away.
狂ったふりしてさらけ出すように
As if acting crazy to expose it all,
救いものをそんなもんだって
if that's what salvation is...
あきらめてもいいからバッドエンドなんかを
It's fine to give up on such a bad ending.
もう どうなってもいいや
I don't care what happens anymore!
縛られたい 燃えたいから
I want to be bound, because I want to burn.
いつの日か忘れちゃって
Someday, I'll forget it all.
分かんないなんて
Saying "I don't understand" like that...
感情の絞り挟んで
Squeezing my emotions out,
特別なラストシーン
a special final scene...
惑う
wandering in confusion.
ミッドナイト逃避行
A midnight escape
温もり感じる距離まで引き寄せて
Pull me close enough to feel your warmth
月の涙が降ったこの夜はまるで
This night where the moon's tears fell is like...
ストレンジャー 愛を叫ぶ
...a stranger crying out for love.
まっさかさまに落ちていった
Plunging headfirst,
無重力 ミッドナイト逃避行
a weightless midnight escape.
秘密の裏側 交じり合って 虜
The flip side of secrets intertwining, leaving us captivated.
一切合切 持っていって
Take away everything I have,
嘘偽りなく 人生をさあ
and show me a life with no lies.
交じり合う星に想いはせて
Directing my thoughts to the merging stars,
月が綺麗だなんて言うのは全て
saying "the moon is beautiful" is all...
嘘、愛を叫ぶ
...a lie, as I cry out my love.
回る 回る 右回りの惨劇
Spinning, spinning, a clockwise tragedy.
混ざる 交ざる 交ざるの ゾクゾク
Mixing, merging, are we blending? Thrilling me...
鼓動のままに 狂うように 高鳴る衝動
...with a pounding impulse, driving me crazy, just like my heartbeat.
もう、どうなってもいいや
I don't care what happens anymore.
つまんないデイズもう散々ね！ 奇跡願っているだけの人生
Boring days are already over! A life where you're just wishing for miracles
watch me do... 呪術秘中トリック無しのマジック
watch me do... Magic without any tricks or secrets
I wanna be free! だってまだふりだし
I wanna be free! Because I'm still at the starting line
(the party ain't started) hey タクシー ちょっと宇宙迄
(the party ain't started) Hey taxi, take me to space for a bit
秒針は音を立てて夜を急かす 魔物のよう
The second hand, like a monster, ticks loudly, urging the night
人生は一瞬にして
Life is magic
溶ける魔法
that melts away in an instant.
それならば駆け抜けて想い通り！
If that's the case, then run through it as you wish!
おしゃまな馬車飛び乗って drivin'
Jump on the playful carriage and start drivin'
あたしは大変身メイクアップ！
I'm in the middle of a great transformation, make-up!
我が儘のまにまに燦きに注意
Be careful not to get caught up in selfishness
洒落た街で dancin'
Dancing in a stylish city
左様ならグッバイ劣等感
If that's the case, goodbye inferiority complex
何時かは喝采 クラップ オウ デ エンス
Someday, applause from the audience
皆々御唱和あれ！
Everyone, join in!
bibbidi bobbidi boowa
混絡がっても仕様が無い ガラスシューズで踊る tonight
Even if it's chaotic, there's no other way, dancing in glass shoes tonight
bibbidi bobbidi boowa
今夜に明日など無い ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょう？
There's no tomorrow tonight, so those who dance freely win, right?
dance！ ラリラリホー
Dance! La la la li ho
どんな問題も解は一つ
Every problem has only one solution
白紙も正解も間違いも愛す
Love blank papers, correct answers, and mistakes
本当のあたしの理想
My true ideal
何だか世界は限界の気配がして
The world seems to have limits I can feel
ただただ安心じゃあ心配
Just being safe is worrying
今すぐ jumpin' out
Jumpin' out right now
chitty chitty bang bang chitty bang bang
唯々諾々に危機感抱く日々に
In days when I feel an urgent crisis
ぎりぎり爆発気味
Explosive feelings are at their limit
たった今発散してしまおうか
Should I let it all out now?
まだまだBB弾 巧妙に乱射
Still firing away BB pellets skillfully
一発じゃあ撃ち足りないわ
One shot is not enough
ついに導き出した君にアンサー
Finally, I found the answer for you
灰に成る迄踊って居よう
Dance until we turn to ash
bibbidi bobbidi boowa
おしゃまな馬車飛び乗って drivin'
Jump on the playful carriage and start drivin'
あたしは大変身メイクアップ！
I'm in the middle of a great transformation, make-up!
我が儘のまにまに燦きに注意
Be careful not to get caught up in selfishness
洒落た街で dancin'
Dancing in a stylish city
左様ならグッバイ劣等感
If that's the case, goodbye inferiority complex
何時かは喝采 クラップ オウ デ エンス
Someday, applause from the audience
皆々御唱和あれ！
Everyone, join in!
bibbidi bobbidi boowa
混絡がっても仕様が無い ガラスシューズで踊る tonight
Even if it's chaotic, there's no other way, dancing in glass shoes tonight
bibbidi bobbidi boowa
今夜に明日など無い ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょう？
There's no tomorrow tonight, so those who dance freely win, right?
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
ということで、二曲お届けさせていただきました。皆さん、楽しんでますか？
So, I have performed two songs for you. Is everyone having fun?
今回は全編アコースティック編成ということで、今までの生誕ライブにはないしっとりとしたね、テイストでお送りしていこうと思いますよ。
This time, with a fully acoustic setup, I'll be delivering a mellow vibe that hasn't been seen in my past birthday concerts.
8周年の感謝の気持ちを込めて、じっくりと音楽に浸ってもらえると嬉しいです。
With gratitude for my 8th anniversary, I hope you can deeply immerse yourselves in the music.
それでは次の曲聴いてください、月に向かって撃て！
Now, please listen to the next song, "Shoot towards the Moon"!
Ooh...
眺めているばかり
I'm only ever watching you,
手を伸ばして思い出す
reaching out my hand as I remember...
汚れたくないわ、ねぇ
I don't want to get dirty, you know?
聞かせたい声
The voice I want you to hear.
幾多のバグのせいだ
It's because of so many bugs.
君が誰なんだか知っていた
I already knew who you were.
証明しよう
Let's prove...
僕らは本当はどうしたいだけ
what we really want to do.
逃げたいと耳塞いだ
I covered my ears, wanting to run away,
静かな心臓を
beating my quiet heart...
叩いてたすけたまい
Please save me.
変わらない表情に
Thrusting the answer...
答えを突き立てて
into that unchanging expression,
情熱を 月に向かって撃て
shoot your passion towards the moon,
スナイパー
sniper!
未来はどうやら君次第
It seems the future is up to you.
喉が渇いたって
Even if my throat runs dry,
後悔はないわ
I have no regrets.
振り向いて埋めるの
Turning around to fill that
99%
小指には衝動
The impulse on my pinky finger,
本当はどうしたいだけ
what is it we really want to do?
合図してハートビート 宙に舞わせて
Signal me, heartbeat, send it dancing into the air!
Ah, ah, fly me to the moon
Ah, ah, 独りで fly me to the moon
Ah, ah, fly me to the moon all alone.
Ah, ah, fly me to the moon
Ah, ah
歩き疲れた風も
Even the wind tired of walking,
ぶつかり合った悔しさも
and the frustration of clashing with each other,
向き合うように照らす
will shine upon us so we can face them.
糧になれ
Let it become our strength!
もしも人生が10分なら
If life were only ten minutes long,
7分は無駄だった言葉のケチャップに
seven minutes would be wasted on ketchup of words.
胸躍るようなアトラクションでタッチダウン
Touch down with a heart-pounding attraction!
臆病も隙間も燃やしていけ ロックスター
Burn away both cowardice and gaps, rockstar!
まだ見ぬゴールは君次第
The unseen goal is up to you.
夢を照らし合った軌道上で
On the orbit where we illuminated our dreams,
吸い込んで一息 99%
inhaling a breath, 99%.
甘い嘘で塞いで
Blocking it with sweet lies,
本当はどうしたいだけ
what is it we really want to do?
追いつくわ ハートビート 追いかけて
Chasing it, my heartbeat will catch up.
証明しよう 届くまで
Let's prove it until it reaches.
情熱を 月に向かって撃て スナイパー
Shoot your passion towards the moon, sniper!
未来は今日も僕ら次第
Today, the future is up to us as well.
誰が笑ったって後悔はないわ
No matter who laughs, I have no regrets.
振り向いて埋めるの 99%
Turning around to fill that 99%.
小指には衝動
The impulse on my pinky finger,
本当はどうしたいだけ
what is it we really want to do?
合図してハートビート 宙に舞わせて
Signal me, heartbeat, send it dancing into the air!
Ah, ah, fly me to the moon
Ah, ah, 独りで fly me to the moon
Ah, ah, fly me to the moon all alone.
Ah, ah, fly me to the moon
Ah, ah
飛び込んできて fly me to the moon
Jump on in and fly me to the moon!
Ah, ah, fly me to the moon
Ah, ah, あなただけに fly me to the moon
Ah, ah, only for you, fly me to the moon.
Ah, ah
綺麗事を吐くその口が
Because the mouth that speaks lip service...
君のことを苦しめるから
only ends up hurting you,
同じことばかりの日々に ああ
In these days where the same things repeat, ah...
意味を求めて寄り添い合うの
we nestle together, searching for meaning.
ひしめき合うカラーフィルターの奥で笑ってる
Smiling behind crowded color filters.
散々恨んだ狡猾さが
The cunningness I hated so much...
今、自分なりの生き方なのに
has now become my own way of living.
潔癖な思考に縛られたままで
But still bound by my fastidious thoughts,
唇を噛む
I bite my lip...
強がるくせに
despite acting tough.
分かってない
Constantly pretending...
ああ
Ah,
素振りをしてばかり
not to understand.
綺麗事を吐くその口が嫌いだから
I sing because I hate the mouth...
歌を歌うんだ
that speaks lip service.
諦めているその顔が
Your resigned face...
僕のことを曇らせる
only clouds my heart.
こんな声だって伝わらなくて
Even if a voice like this won't reach you,
もっと完璧な言葉を紡ぎたくて
and I want to spin more perfect words,
ずっと欲張って
constantly being greedy,
きっと間違えて
surely making mistakes...
今日も転げ落ちる
I keep falling down again today,
不完全
incomplete...
...な朝
...an imperfect morning.
本音も言えない日常にはただ
To a daily life where I can't even speak my true feelings,
「理想なんて」と嘲笑う声
there's only a voice mocking, "As if ideals matter."
言い返す言葉も選べずに
Unable to even choose the words to talk back,
ただ増していく痛み
the pain just continues to grow.
虚勢を張る衝動で隠して
Hiding behind the urge to bluff,
綺麗なままで生きてたいのか
do you want to live while remaining beautiful?
諦めを塗り重ねて
Layering over resignations,
「本当」が見えなくなってしまうんだ
the "truth" ends up becoming completely invisible.
綺麗事を吐くその口が
That mouth that spews out pleasantries...
Because I hate that mouth that spews out pleasantries,
嫌いだから歌を歌うんだ
I sing.
諦めているその顔が
That face of resignation
君の事を苦しめる
is what makes you suffer.
こんな声だって伝わらなくて
Even if a voice like this won't reach you,
もっと完璧な言葉を紡ぎたくて
I want to spin more perfect words.
ずっと欲張って
Always being greedy,
きっと間違えて
and surely making mistakes...
それでも歌おう
Even so, let's sing,
不完全だから
because we are imperfect.
ありがとうございました
Thank you very much!
楽しんでますか？
Are you enjoying yourselves?
さあ、みんなね、武道館再演でだした
So, everyone, about that teaser for the major announcement
あの重大発表のティザー、あの内容が気になっているころなのではないでしょうか？
we showed at the Budokan encore... You must be wondering about its contents by now, right?
それからみんな、もちろん見つけてくれましたよね？
And of course, you all found it, right?
先週の月曜日から、ある場所で屋外広告もね、出ていたりして
Since last Monday, outdoor advertisements have also been put up in a certain place,
きっと今頃ね、何が起きるんだって
and I'm sure by now you are wondering what's going to happen,
ただならぬ空気を感じて、どぎまぎしているんじゃないかなと思うんですけれども、
feeling an unusual vibe and getting all nervous, but...
まずはね、言葉じゃなくて、今日の告知に向けて
first of all, rather than using words, for today's announcement,
音楽に込めてみんなに伝えたいなと思い、こういう編成で今回やらせてもらっております。
I wanted to convey it to you through music, which is why we are performing with this acoustic setup today.
アコースティックってなんかエモくて、今までのことをこう、思い返すような
There's something emotional about acoustic music, as if you're looking back on the past...
なんかノスタルジーな気持ちになったりしますよね。
It makes you feel a sort of nostalgic feeling, doesn't it?
いつもはテンションを上げてくれるようなあの曲が、今日はね、また違った形でみんなに響いたらいいなと思って
I sang that song, which usually hypes everyone up, hoping it would resonate with you in a different way today,
歌わせていただいております。
as I perform it for you now.
楽曲のアレンジもそうだし、この生誕配信自体もそうだし、
Not just the song arrangement, but also this birthday stream itself...
新しい一面をね、見せながらも、
While showing you a new side of me,
何よりこの8年間、みんなでね、一緒にやってきた、紡いできた
more than anything, over these past 8 years that we've spent and spun together,
絆みたいなものが、しっかり感じられるライブにできたら嬉しいです。
I hope this live performance allows us to truly feel that bond.
それでは、次の曲に行きましょう。
With that, let's move on to the next song.
ムーンライト
Moonlight.
遠くまで歩こうよ、裸足で
Let's walk far away, barefoot,
小さな幸せを見つけて
seeking out tiny bits of happiness.
湿った月が窓を覗いて
The damp moon peers through the window
こっちへおいでと笑った
and laughs, telling us to come over.
似た者同士なんだよね、案外
We are two of a kind, surprisingly,
分かり合えない部分も安牌
with our misunderstandings being a safe bet.
月明かりをめくった残像
The afterimages that peeled back the moonlight...
誰かにとっての普通をしよう
Let's behave "normally" for someone's sake.
私と踊ってよ、ムーンライト
Dance with me, Moonlight.
ねえ、こっちであそぼう サニーサイド
Hey, let's play over here on the sunny side.
隠し事ばっかの インサイド
Inside, it's nothing but secrets.
ねえ、こっちであそぼうよ ミッドナイト
Hey, let's play over here at midnight.
この、重たいカーテンを開け去って
Let's open up these heavy curtains
嘘みたいな夜を抜け出そう
and escape into this dream-like night.
まだ、やることばっかで 忙しいけど おやすみ
We're still busy with so much to do, but goodnight.
あの、一等星になって 街をハイジャックしようぜ
Let's become that first-magnitude star and hijack the town.
この、メロウな今日を ずっと泳いでいこう
Let's keep swimming through this mellow day forever.
泳いでいこう
Let's keep swimming on...
街明かりを奪って
Stealing the city lights,
月で待ち合わせ
we'll meet up on the moon.
届きそうで届かない
So close yet so far out of reach,
あなたはムーンライト
you are my moonlight.
理由も無く寂しい夜が来て
For no reason, a lonely night arrives,
古くなっていく希望の上で眠りたい
and I want to sleep on top of fading hopes.
似た者同士なんだから厄介
We are two of a kind, which makes it troublesome.
隠し事すらも抱えて厄介
Holding even secrets inside is troublesome.
まだやることばっかりで忙しいけど おやすみ
I still have so much to do and I'm busy, but goodnight.
あの光の方へ
Toward that light,
どこか遠い方へ
to somewhere far away...
このメロウな今日をずっと泳いでいこう
Let's keep swimming through this mellow today.
月日ない闇の種
The timeless seed of darkness,
話を聞かせて
let me hear your story.
私とあなただけの世界で
In a world that belongs only to you and me...
あの 一等星になって 街をハイジャックしようぜ
Let's become that first-magnitude star and hijack the town!
このメロウな今日をずっと泳いでいこう
Let's keep swimming through this mellow today.
穴だらけの心で
With a heart full of holes,
あなただけを思って
thinking only of you...
眠れそうで眠れない こんな夜は
On a night like this, when I'm on the verge of sleep but can't...
私と踊ってよ ムーンライト
Dance with me, Moonlight.
ねえ こっちで遊ぼう サニーサイド
Hey, let's play over here on the Sunnyside.
隠し事ばっかの インサイド
Filled with nothing but secrets inside.
ねえ こっちで遊ぼうよ ミッドナイト
Hey, let's play over here, Midnight.
街明かりを奪って
Stealing the city lights,
月で待ち合わせ
we'll meet up on the moon.
届きそうで届かない
So close yet so far out of reach,
あなたはムーンライト
you are my moonlight.
遠くまで歩こうよ 裸足で
Let's walk far away, barefoot,
小さな幸せを見つけて
finding little pieces of happiness.
湿った月が窓を覗いて
The damp moon peeked through the window,
こっちへおいでと笑った
and smiled, saying "come over here."
似た者同士なんだよね 案外
We are two of a kind, surprisingly.
分かり合えない部分も安牌
Even the parts we can't understand are a safe bet.
月明かりをめくった残像
The afterimage left by turning over the moonlight...
私にとっての普通でいよう
Let's keep it as my ordinary.
実はここから、スペシャルゲストに来てもらっています。
Actually, starting from here, I have a special guest with us!
さあ、誰かわかるかな？
Now, does anyone know who it is?
それでは、お呼びしましょう。
Well then, let's call them out.
イノタクさん！
Inotaku-san!
お久しぶりです。
It's been a while!
改めてよろしくお願いします。
Once again, pleased to have you here.
来てくれて嬉しいです、ありがとうございます。
I'm so glad you could make it, thank you.
ここからは、イノタクさんにも入ってもらって、
From here on, with Inotaku-san joining us as well,
さらなる特別編成で何曲か続けてお届けしていきますよ。
we will perform a few songs in an even more special setup.
イノタクさん、準備はいいですか？
Inotaku-san, are you ready?
よろしくお願いします。
Let's do this.
それでは聞いてください、夜を待つよ。
So then, please listen to... "Waiting for the Night."
夜を待つよ
[Title: Waiting for the Night]
I'll wait for the night
夜を待つよ
I'll wait for the night...
待つのよ
waiting...
今日もまたばっちりしっかり決まって
Today, too, is perfectly and firmly set,
君ははっきりきっぱり歌って
as you clearly and decisively sing.
明けない夜は
"A night that never dawns...
そんなものはないよと
there is no such thing," you say.
椰子の木がゆっくりゆっくりそよいで
As the palm trees gently and slowly sway,
僕はやっぱりやっぱりわかって
I indeed, after all, understand.
ただひたすらに
Solely and earnestly,
夜を待つよ
I'll wait for the night.
このままじゃだんだんだめになりそう
At this rate, I feel like I'll slowly fall apart.
夜を待つよ
Waiting for the night,
waiting for the night.
きっと散々だめな目に遭いそう
I'm sure I'll meet with terrible luck.
夜を待つよ
Waiting for the night,
待つのよ
waiting...
耐え抜いて散々雨に降られて
Enduring through, completely drenched by the rain,
夜を待つよ
I'll wait for the night,
君を待つよ
wait for you,
待つのよ
waiting...
今は待つのよ
right now, I'm waiting.
濡れたまんま行き先を紡ぐのよ
Still wet, I will weave our destination.
行き当たりばったりにこり笑って
Haphazardly, with a gentle smile,
今日をボトなフリして
pretending to be childish today...
あかさたなさな はまらないよの
a-ka-sa-ta-na, it doesn't fit...
はまらない夜です
It's a night where things don't fit.
あっちでこっちで踊って
Dancing here and there,
君ははったりばかりかまして
you're just talking big and playing bluff,
ぼくは
while I...
夜を待つよ
wait for the night.
このままじゃだんだんだめになりそう
At this rate, I feel like I'll slowly fall apart.
夜を待つよ 夜を待つよ
I'll wait for the night, wait for the night.
もっと混沌の海が理想
More chaotic seas would be ideal.
夜を待つよ 待つのよ
I'll wait for the night, I will wait.
美しい本当よりもひしゃげた
Rather than a beautiful truth, a crushed...
夜を待つよ
night, I will wait for it...
君を待つよ 待つのよ
waiting for you, I'll wait.
今は待つのよ
For now, I will wait.
いつかきっときっかけはくるのよ
Surely, the trigger will come someday.
唇でゆっくりゆっくり騙して
Deceive me slowly, slowly with your lips.
ぼくはポップでチープなふりして
I'll pretend to be pop and cheap,
真夜中までの夕暮れを泳いでは
swimming through the twilight until midnight,
もののけはうっとりうっそり笑って
the monsters smile, enchanted and deceitful,
導火線が燃える中で今
while the fuse is burning, now...
嘘をつくの
I tell a lie,
夜が来るまでは
until the night comes.
夜が明ける千年前からぼくら
Since a thousand years before the dawn, we...
夜を待つよ 夜を待つよ
wait for the night, wait for the night.
君がぜんぜんわからないから
Because I don't understand you at all,
夜を待つよ 待つのよ
I'll wait for the night, I'll wait.
無理筋なペンチャン待ちでもいいの
Even a far-fetched inner-edge wait is fine.
夜を待つよ 夜を待つよ
Wait for the night, wait for the night.
待つのよ 君を待つよ
I'll wait, wait for you.
そうよもっと切先を研ぐのよ
That's right, sharpen the blade even more.
最後最後絶対笑うのよ
In the very end, we will definitely laugh.
君を待つのよ
I will wait for you.
最後最後笑うのはぼくらだ
In the very end, the ones who laugh will be us.
だって僕は星だから
Because I am a star,
Stellar Stellar
きっと君はもう気づいていた
Surely you had already noticed,
僕の心の奥で描いた
envisioned deep within my heart,
それがこれから話す陳腐なモノローグさ
that's the clichéd monologue I'm about to tell.
ずっと言えない言葉があった
There were words I could never say,
壊せない壁があったんだ ずっとさ保存
walls I could never break, all this time.
ふっと香り立つ朝の匂いが
The scent of morning suddenly wafting in the air
どうしようもなく憎らしくて保存
is so unbearably detestable to me,
部屋の隅で膝を抱えて震えていた
as I sat in a corner, clutching my knees and trembling.
太陽なんていらないから
I don't need the sun anyway,
明けないでいて
so please don't let the dawn break.
その手を伸ばして 誰か届くように
Reach out that hand, so it may reach someone,
僕だって君と同じ
because I'm just like you,
特別なんかじゃないから
nothing special.
そうさぼくはよるを歌うよ stellar stellar
Yes, I will sing of the night, stellar stellar,
ありったけの輝きで
with all the brightness I have.
今宵音楽はずっとずっと止まない
Tonight, the music will never, ever stop.
そうだ僕がずっとかなりたかったのは
That's right, what I've always wanted to be
待ってるシンデレラじゃないさ
isn't a Cinderella who just waits,
迎えに行く王子様だ
but a prince who goes to rescue her.
だって僕は星だから保存
Because I am a star...
なんてありふれた話なんだ
What a commonplace story it is,
理想だけ書き連ねていた
just listing all my ideals,
ノートの隅に眠るほんのワンシーンだ
a mere single scene sleeping in the corner of my notebook.
きっとあの星も泣いてるんだ
Surely that star is crying too,
明日なんて
without tomorrow ever...
...このままでいて
...stay just as you are.
その手を伸ばして
Reach out your hand,
誰かに届くように
so it may reach someone.
本当に大切なものは
The things that are truly precious
目に見えないみたいなんだ
seem to be invisible to the eyes.
そうさ僕は夜を歌うよステラ ステラ
That's right, I'll sing of the night, Stellar, Stellar,
ありのまま考えないで
just as you are, without thinking.
この音楽はきっときっと止まらない
This music will surely, surely never stop.
そうさ僕はずっと泣きたかったのは
That's right, the reason I've wanted to cry all this time
会えない会えない君のせいじゃないさ
isn't because I can't meet you.
救いに行く今を
I'm coming to rescue you now,
歌う
as I sing!
夢見がちな
A dreamy
おとぎ話
fairy tale...
そうさ僕は夜を歌うよステラ ステラ
That's right, I'll sing of the night, Stellar, Stellar,
ありったけの輝きで
with all the brilliance I have.
この音楽はずっとずっと止まらない
This music will forever and ever never stop.
そうさ僕は愛を歌うよステラ ステラ
That's right, I'll sing of love, Stellar, Stellar,
広い宇宙の真ん中で
in the middle of this vast universe.
この音楽はきっときっと止まらない
This music will surely, surely never stop.
そうさ僕はずっと泣きたかったのは
That's right, the reason I've wanted to cry all this time
待って死んでシンデレラじゃないさ
isn't because I'm a waiting Cinderella.
迎えに行く王子様だ
I'm the prince coming to rescue you!
だって僕は星だから
Because I am a star!
そうさ僕は星だから
That's right, because I am a star!
ステラ ステラ
Stellar, Stellar...
「Midnight Grand Orchestra」で「夜を待つよ」、そして「Stellar Stellar」でした！いかがでしたでしょうか？
Those were "Yoru wo Matsu yo" by Midnight Grand Orchestra, and "Stellar Stellar"! How did you like them?
そしてイノタクさん、今回のレンジめっちゃいいですね！
And Inotaku-san, this arrangement is so amazing!
いや、めちゃくちゃ良かった。アレンジの皆様ありがとうございました。ありがとうございます。素晴らしい。
It was absolutely wonderful. Thank you to all the arrangers. Thank you. It was amazing.
イノタクさんもギター最高でしたよ。
Inotaku-san, your guitar playing was awesome too.
いや〜緊張したわ〜。ありがとうございました。はい。
Man, I was so nervous. Thank you very much. Yes.
いつもね、聴いてたあの曲がこんな感じにアレンジされるんだっていうね
It's so exciting to hear a song I always listen to get arranged like this,
いい意味での裏切りというか、すごいワクワクするアレンジになっているんじゃないかなと思います。
like a betrayal in a good way. I think it creates a really thrilling arrangement.
そしてね、なんかここまでたくさんこの曲たちを歌ってきて、
Also, having sung these songs so much up until now,
もう8年やってきたんだなっていうのを改めて実感しましたし、
it really sank in again that I've been doing this for 8 years.
これからもね、星街すいせい、そして「Midnight Grand Orchestra」も、末永くよろしくお願いいたします。
Please continue to support Hoshimachi Suisei and Midnight Grand Orchestra for a long time to come.
ということで、特別ゲストのタク・イノウエさんでした！ありがとうございました、タク・イノウエでした。
With that, our special guest was Taku Inoue-san! Thank you very much, I was Taku Inoue.
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
さて、楽しい時間はあっという間というところで、
Now, time flies when you're having fun,
次がいよいよ、最後の曲になります。
and the next one will finally be our last song.
私自身、この曲が一番アコースティックになったらどうなるんだろうという感じで、
Personally, I was wondering how this song would sound in an acoustic version,
すごいね、バンドメンバーさんと合わせるのワクワクしておりました。
and I was so excited to play it with the band members.
皆さんにも楽しんでもらえたら嬉しいです。
I hope you all enjoy it.
それでは、最後に聴いてください。「ソワレ」。
And now, please listen to our last song, "Soiree".
あの黄昏も
Even that twilight,
降りたたんだ街は
in the city we stepped down into...
じゃじゃ、お墨付きはあいつだ
Yeah, yeah, he's got the stamp of approval.
灯りも消して
Turn off the lights,
始めよう 幕を引いて
and let's begin, draw the curtains.
見上げる願いを
Looking up at my wish,
あなたの様に
just like you.
変わらず在っていたい
I want to remain unchanged.
きらめきのヴェールを
The glittering veil,
手元に 放棄もしない
I won't let go of it.
描いて
As I draw,
またたいた ソワレ
the soiree twinkled.
今だ、音色を立てて
Now, let the melody ring out,
太陽の目を見張って
staring wide-eyed at the sun,
大脱走さ、逃げ出そうぜ
it's a great escape, let's run away.
朝が満ちる空を待とう
Let's wait for the sky where morning fills.
栞を挟んだら
Once we place a bookmark,
行かなくちゃ
we have to go.
ソワレ、夜が明けるまでは
Soiree, until the night breaks,
もう少し保存
just a little longer,
このままで
stay like this.保存
あの日に交わした言葉
The words we exchanged that day,
赤めさしたって 止まない
even if they made me blush, won't stop.
時間が積まろうと
Even if time piles up,
容易く遮る
blocking it so easily.
未来の話を
Let's talk about the future,保存
涼しそうに聞いて保存
listening with an unbothered look.
君に
To you,
違う世界に
who has gone
迷い込んだって
to a different world,
夢は続いていく
the dream goes on.
おやすみに 変わる様
So that it turns into a goodnight,
鳴り止まないメロディ 届けて
deliver the melody that won't stop ringing.
見逃すな ソワレ
Don't miss it, soiree.
僕らが目撃者だ
We are the eyewitnesses.
早急に 手を伸ばした
I reached out my hand in a hurry.
水平線が
Even if the horizon
邪魔したって
gets in our way,
とめどなく日々を繋ぐ
unendingly connecting the days.
架け橋を渡ったら
Once we cross the bridge,
いつの日か保存
someday,
ソワレ、君に届くまでさ
soiree, until it reaches you.
何度でも
No matter how many times,
呼び声を
I'll call out,
伝って
tracing along,保存
消えない 奇跡辿って保存
and follow the miracles that won't fade.
歌って保存
Singing,
幾星霜の果て
at the end of countless years,
どこまでも
no matter how far.
一晩中 語り尽くせない
Even a whole night isn't enough to talk about
悲劇も
this tragedy.
一晩中 語り明かせたら
But if we can talk all night long,
喜劇になっていく
it will turn into a comedy.
伝って
Trace along,
聞かせてよ
let me hear it.
誓って
I swear,
一筋の
a single ray of...
伝って
trace it...
あぁ
Ah...
またたいた ソワレ
The soiree twinkled.
今だ、音色を立てて
Now, let the melody ring out,
太陽の目を見張って
staring wide-eyed at the sun,
大脱走さ、逃げ出そうぜ
it's a great escape, let's run away.
朝が満ちる空を待とう
Let's wait for the sky where morning fills.
約束だ、ソワレ
It's a promise, soiree,
僕らが眠るまでは
until we fall asleep.
何度も
No matter how many times,保存
もっと明日を
we will sing
歌おう
of tomorrow.
拝啓、ソワレ
Dear soiree,
君が見つめる
this is our story
僕たちの
that you are watching over.
物語
Story.
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
以上、星街すいせいでした！
This was Hoshimachi Suisei!
配信の方、以上です。お疲れ様でしたー！
That's all for the stream. Thank you for your hard work!
お疲れ様でしたー！
Thank you for your hard work!
お疲れ様でした！
Great job!
あ、足元お気をつけてください
Ah, please watch your step.
暗くなってます、お気をつけください
It's dark, please watch your step.
お疲れ様でした！
Thank you for your hard work!
お疲れ様！
Great job!
お疲れ様でした！
Thank you for your hard work!保存
お疲れ様です。配信見てくれてましたか？
Thanks for your hard work. Were you watching the stream?
もちろんです。本当に、お疲れ様でした
Of course. Really, thank you for your hard work.
この後、あの件発表してきます
After this, I'm going to announce that matter.
胸を張って、自信を持ってお話ししてきてください
Stand tall, and talk with confidence.保存
はい、頑張ります！
Yes, I'll do my best!
改めて、5周年記念
Once again, for my 5th Anniversary
生誕配信を見てくれて本当にありがとうございます。
and Birthday stream, thank you so much for watching.
今日は、私、星街すいせいから
Today, I, Hoshimachi Suisei,
皆さんへ重大な発表があります。
have a major announcement for all of you.
これまで長年、カバーさん、
For many years, Cover Corporation,
そしてホロライブプロダクションには本当にお世話になってきました。
and Hololive Production have taken great care of me.
長年の夢だった日本武道館など、
With Nippon Budokan being my long-time dream,
たくさんの支えのおかげで夢を1つずつ叶えていくことができました。
I was able to make my dreams come true one by one.
感謝の気持ちを伝えられる機会がこれまであまりなかったのですが、
I haven't had many chances to express my gratitude,
谷郷さんをはじめ、ホロライブのタレントのみんな、
but starting with Tanigo-san, the Hololive talents,
スタッフの皆さん、関係してくださった皆さんに、心から感謝しています。ありがとうございます。
the staff, and everyone involved, thank you from the bottom of my heart.
その上で、東京ドームという次の目標に到達するためには、
On top of that, in order to reach my next goal, the Tokyo Dome,
これからどうすればいいのかを考えてきました。
I've been thinking about what I should do next.
昔に比べると、たくさんの方に見ていただけるようになりましたが、
Compared to before, I have so many people watching me now,
それでも、まだまだ超えなければいけない壁がたくさんあります。
but there are still many walls I need to overcome.
色んなものと真剣に向き合い、
After facing various things seriously
そして、考え抜いた結果、1つの大きな決断を下しました。
and thinking it through, I've made one big decision.
びっくりさせちゃうかもしれませんが、
This might surprise you,
その発表を今日、この場所でさせてください。
but please let me make that announcement here today.
[STUDIO STELLAR]
[星街すいせい 個人事務所設立]
[Hoshimachi Suisei / Establishment of Personal Office]
ということで、この度、星街すいせいは
And so, I, Hoshimachi Suisei,
個人事務所を設立することになりました！名称は「STUDIO STELLAR」！
have established my own personal office, STUDIO STELLAR!
今後の私個人の活動、日頃の配信、
My future personal activities, daily streams,
音楽活動、メディア出演、タイアップ、
music career, media appearances, tie-ups,
グッズ展開などなど、すべてこの「STUDIO STELLAR」を拠点に行っていくことになります。
merchandise, and more, will all be based here at STUDIO STELLAR.
と、こんな真面目なトーンで話すと、
Now, talking in such a serious tone might make you think,
「え？すいちゃんホロライブ卒業！？」なんてね、思っちゃう人もいるんじゃないでしょうか？
"Wait, is Sui-chan graduating from Hololive?!"
安心してください！
Rest assured!
ホロライブプロダクションとしての星街すいせいの活動も、これまで通り継続していきます！
My activities as a member of Hololive Production will continue as usual!
ホロライブの大好きなみんなとの活動は、引き続き思い切り楽しみつつ、
While I continue to enjoy activities with my Hololive friends,
個人としてのさらなる高みを目指す場所が「STUDIO STELLAR」という住み分けです。
STUDIO STELLAR will be where I aim for greater heights as an individual.
もっともっと大きなステージに立つための
This is a positive and major decision
前向きで大きな決断なので、ぜひこれからも応援してもらえると凄く凄く嬉しいです！
to stand on bigger stages, so I'd be happy if you continue to support me!
ちなみに、事務所の公式SNSもできましたので、
By the way, the office's official social media is now live,
今すぐフォローしてください！
so please go follow it right away!
IDは、
The ID is
アットマーク、エスティアンダーバーステラーアンダーバーインフォです！
@st_stellar_info!
この個人事務所設立をきっかけに、
With the establishment of this personal office,
星街すいせいを構成するあらゆるクリエイティブをリニューアルしていきます。
all the creative elements that define Hoshimachi Suisei will be renewed.
どんどん発表していきますよ、準備はいいですか？
I'll be announcing them one after another, are you ready?
それでは1つ目。
First of all,
長年愛用してきた星街すいせいのロゴをリニューアルさせていただきました！こちら！
I have renewed the Hoshimachi Suisei logo! Here it is!
これまでの歴史とトーンはしっかり踏襲しつつ、
While keeping the history and tone,
今の時代に、そして今の私に一番フィットする形にデザインし直しました。
it has been redesigned to best fit the current era and who I am now.
さらに、ずっと欲しかった私のシンボルマークも、
On top of that, a brand-new symbol mark
なんと新しく誕生しましたよ！こちら。いかがですか？可愛いね、王冠マークになっております。
that I've always wanted has been created! Here it is, a cute crown mark.
お次は、アーティスト写真です。どうぞ！
Next up is the artist photo. Here you go!
はい！今回は、夜の海で撮影してもらいました。
Yes! This time, it was shot by the sea at night.
これからの果てしない旅を感じさせる、お気に入りの一枚になっております。
It's my favorite, giving a sense of the endless journey ahead.
まだまだありますよ！
There's still more!
実は、これまでずっとなかったすいちゃんの公式ウェブサイトが、ついにオープンします！
My official website, which we never had before, is finally opening!
最新情報だったり、随時アップデートしていくので、毎日チェックしてくださいね。
We'll be updating it with the latest info, so please check it every day.
そしてそして！皆さん、きっと待望であろう、
And finally, the one you've all been waiting for,
公式ファンクラブも設立が決定しました！名前は「星詠み」！
my official fan club is being established! Its name is Hoshiyomi!
を、ファンクラブの名前にさせていただきました。
...became the name of my official fan club.
これからも、もっとみんなの近くで
いろんなことを発信していきたいと思っております。
I hope to share all sorts of things with you
from an even closer distance.
ファンクラブ限定グッズが買えたり、
チケットの先行申し込みができたり、
You can buy fan club-exclusive merchandise
and apply for advance tickets...
会報誌、ラジオコンテンツなどなど、
ファンクラブのために色々準備しているので、
as well as enjoy newsletters, radio content, and more.
We have so much in store for you!
入会をお待ちしております！
I'll be waiting for you to join!
入会はこの配信終了後、21時から経つ！
Registrations open tonight at 9:00 PM,
right after this stream ends!
ファンクラブができたということは、
次に何が来るかお分かりですよね？
Now that we have a fan club,
you know what's coming next, right?
それでは、VTRどうぞ！
With that, let's watch the video!
[星街すいせい アリーナツアー2026
「Once Upon a Stellar」開催決定]
[Hoshimachi Suisei Arena Tour 2026
"Once Upon a Stellar" Announced]
[神奈川：Kアリーナ横浜
9.08(Tue) & 09.09(Wed)]
[Kanagawa: K-Arena Yokohama
Sept 8 (Tue) & Sept 9 (Wed)]
[兵庫：GLION ARENA KOBE
10.21(Wed)]
[Hyogo: GLION ARENA KOBE
Oct 21 (Wed)]
[愛知：IGアリーナ
11.07(Sat)]
[Aichi: IG Arena
Nov 7 (Sat)]
[福岡：マリンメッセ福岡A館
11.12(Thu)]
[Fukuoka: Marine Messe Fukuoka Hall A
Nov 12 (Thu)]
[本日3月22日 21:00〜
ファンクラブ最速先行抽選受付開始]
[Advance Ticket Lottery begins today,
March 22, at 9:00 PM]
なんと、星街すいせいアリーナツアー、
またしても開催決定！ありがとうございます！ドドン！
Unbelievable! Another Hoshimachi Suisei Arena Tour
has been confirmed! Thank you so much! Ta-da!
タイトルは、「Once Upon a Stellar」。
The title is "Once Upon a Stellar."
今回は、4会場5公演でお届けします。
This time, we will perform five shows
across four venues.
9月8日、9月9日のKアリーナ横浜、
2DAYSを皮切りに、
Starting off with two days at K-Arena Yokohama
on September 8 and 9...
10月21日に、GLION ARENA KOBE、
on October 21, at GLION ARENA KOBE...
11月7日に、名古屋、IGアリーナ、
on November 7, at IG Arena in Nagoya...
そして、11月12日にマリンメッセ福岡A館。
and finally, on November 12,
at Marine Messe Fukuoka Hall A.
星街すいせい初となる、4都市アリーナツアー！
ぜひ遊びに来てください！
This is my first-ever four-city arena tour!
Please come and see me!
お気づきの方もね、いると思うんですけれど、
今回のライブキービジュアルも、Mika Pikazoさんに、か、か、か...
You might have already noticed,
but the key visual for this concert was designed by...
カット！
Cut!
お気づきの方もいるかもしれませんが、
今回のライブキービジュアルは、Mika Pikazo先生に描き下ろしていただきました！
Some of you might have noticed, but the key visual
was illustrated by Mika Pikazo-sensei!
Mika先生、本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much, Mika-sensei!
今回も本当に素敵なキービジュアルでね、
あの、ぜひたくさんね、見てください！
It's such a gorgeous visual once again,
so please take a good look at it!
チケットは、なんと、本日の配信終了後から、
早速ファンクラブ先行申し込みがスタートします！
Unbelievably, fan club advance ticket applications
will start right after this stream ends!
絶対絶対チェックしてくださいね！
So make sure you don't miss it!
はい。次。実は、もう一つ、
騒がれていたあの大きなプロジェクトが動き出します。
Next. Actually, there's another major project
that everyone's been talking about that is finally in motion.
それでは、VTRをどうぞ！
Without further ado, let's watch the video!
切り裂く静寂 全速前進
生み出す引力で 光速のパッセージ
Silence cut open, full speed ahead.
Gravitational force pulling me into a light-speed passage.
アレグロで今日も舞って
わななく轟音
Dancing today in allegro,
a trembling roar.
The show must go on
消えない一拍を もっと紡いで
The show must go on.
Keep spinning a beat that never fades.
打ち鳴らせ今日も万全で
Play it out today, absolutely perfect!
[Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd LIVE "ALLEGRO"
2027年2月11日 幕張メッセ 開催決定]
[Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live "ALLEGRO"
Feb 11, 2027 at Makuhari Messe]
しばらく眠っていたあのプロジェクト、
Midnight Grand Orchestraも、活動を改めて本格化していきます！
That project which had been asleep for a while,
Midnight Grand Orchestra, is resuming full activities!
タイトルは、プロジェクト「ALLEGRO」。
The project title is "ALLEGRO."
日程は、2027年2月11日。
場所は、幕張メッセにてライブを行います。
The concert will be held on February 11, 2027,
at Makuhari Messe.
こちらも本日からファンクラブで先行申し込みができるので、
ぜひぜひ遊びに来てください！
Fan club advance tickets are also available starting today,
so please come and see us!
リリースだったり、タイアップなど、
すでに色々決まっているものもありますので、
With releases, tie-ups, and other things
already lined up...
星街すいせい、そしてMidnight Grand Orchestraの
これからを楽しみにしていてくれると嬉しいです。
I hope you look forward to the future
of Hoshimachi Suisei and Midnight Grand Orchestra.
さて。すごい勢いで情報を出してきましたが、
Well, I've just dropped a massive wave of announcements...
皆さんついてこれておりますでしょうか？
but have you all been able to keep up?
今日発表したことは、全部ね、次の大きな目標に向けて、
Everything announced today is a step
toward my next big goal...
私が本当に頑張りたいと思って、
たくさん悩んだ末に決断をしたことです。
decisions I made after much deliberation
because I truly want to give it my all.
環境は少し変わるかもしれないんですが、
While my environment might change slightly...
星街すいせいはもちろんこれからもずっと、
私らしくあり続けます。
Hoshimachi Suisei will, of course,
continue to stay true to herself.
これからもどうか一緒に夢を追いかけてくれると嬉しいです。
よろしくお願いします！
I would be so happy if you keep chasing
dreams together with me. Thank you!
さて、それでは最後に、
Now then, finally...
３つ、まだ３つもある、３つだけお知らせをして、
今日の配信を終わりたいと思います。
I have three—yes, three more announcements to make
before wrapping up today's stream.
まず1つ目！
First of all!
今日はみなさん、お忘れじゃないですよね？
Everyone, you haven't forgotten today, right?
私の誕生日でもある！ということで
It's also my birthday!
生誕グッズをもちろんご用意しております！
Of course, I have birthday merchandise ready for you!
Tシャツ、ステッカーセット、アクスタ
T-shirt, sticker set, acrylic stand...
全部入りボックスに加えて、ファンクラブ限定のTシャツなどなど
and the full set box, plus the fan club exclusive T-shirt!
どれもデザインにこだわりましたので、ぜひ手に入れてください！
I paid close attention to all the designs, so please get them!
2つ目！
Second of all!
星街すいせいライブツアー 2024 SPECTRA of NOVA
Hoshimachi Suisei Live Tour 2024 SPECTRA of NOVA,
星街すいせい 日本武道館ライブ SUPERNOVA
and Hoshimachi Suisei Nippon Budokan Live SUPERNOVA...
この2つのBlu-rayの通常盤が予約受付開始します！
the standard editions of these two Blu-rays are now open for pre-order!
予約は本日22時からスタートです！
Pre-orders start tonight at 22:00!
今回のBlu-rayは以前のようなセット販売はなく
These Blu-rays will not be sold as a set like before,
ツアー、武道館、それぞれ個別での販売のみになります
but will only be sold individually for the Tour and Budokan.
そしてツアーのBlu-rayは、埼玉公演のみの映像化となっています//そしてツアーのBlu-rayは、埼玉公演のみの映像化となっています
And the Tour Blu-ray features footage only from the Saitama performance.
ただし、特典映像として他のツアー公演の楽曲も一部収録されております
However, as bonus footage, some songs from other tour stops are also included.
ゲストパートとか！何が収録されているかはぜひBlu-rayでチェックしてみてください！
Like the guest parts! Please check the Blu-ray to see what's included!
なお、今回は去年販売したBlu-rayとは仕様が少し異なり
Also, this time, the specs are slightly different from last year's Blu-ray,
ツアーBlu-rayの特典映像以外の特典は付属していませんので、ご注意ください
and no bonuses other than the bonus footage are included, so please be aware.
ただ、その分ね、お買い求めやすい価格になっておりますので
However, they are priced much more affordably instead,
詳しくは特設サイトや公式X、公式Twitterをチェックしてください！
so please check the special site, official X, or official Twitter for details!
そして、3つ目！
And third of all!
みなさん、お待たせしました！
Everyone, thank you for waiting!
毎年恒例ですが、新曲が出ます！
As is our annual tradition, a new song is coming out!
タイトルは、「プリマドンナ」！
The title is "Primadonna"!
この配信が終わった後、21時半からミュージックビデオのプレミア公開が始まります！
After this stream ends, the Music Video premiere starts at 21:30!
これからの星街すいせいの名刺代わりになるような、すごくテンションが上がる曲に仕上がっております
It's a high-energy song that'll serve as a new calling card for Hoshimachi Suisei.
概要欄に貼っているURLから飛べるので、ぜひ楽しみにしていてください！絶対に待機していてください！
You can find the link in the description, so please look forward to it and wait for it!
ということで、以上で星街すいせい8周年記念生誕配信を終わります
And with that, this concludes the Hoshimachi Suisei 8th Anniversary Birthday Stream.
今日は本当にありがとうございました！
Thank you so much for today!
新しいスタジオステラの星街すいせいも、どうかどうかよろしくお願いいたします！
Please continue to support Hoshimachi Suisei at the new Studio Stellar!
それでは、まったねー！
Well then, see ya later!
最後までみてくれてありがとう☆ これからも私は私らしく...
[Text: Thank you for watching until the end! I will continue to be true to myself...]
...みんなと共にあります。
[Text: ...and always stay together with all of you.]
新しい挑戦を続けて、まだ見ぬ世界を見に行こう！
[Text: Let's continue to take on new challenges and see unseen worlds!]
照らす 一筋の light
A single ray of light shining down
注ぐ 無数の 視線 like stars
Countless pouring gazes like stars
独り占め したい その 心
I want to monopolize that heart
幕 が 上がれ ば act one
If the curtains open up, act one
yeah, are you ready now?
すいせい here i come
Suisei, here I come
そこ退けて 譲れないわ my stage
Make way, I won't give up my stage
邪魔しないでよね
So don't get in my way
make up して dress up
I'll make up and dress up
待ってる人がいるの yeah
Because there are people waiting for me, yeah
ところで そちら どちら様ですか？
By the way, who might you be over there?
もういいですか？ 主役って大変だわ
Are we good already? Being the lead is tough
pop, pop, ノイズを消して
Pop, pop, turn off the noise
目と目 逸らさないでね
Keep our eyes locked, don't look away
プリマドンナ
Prima Donna
冷笑にはもうウンザリだわ
I'm already fed up with the sneers
熱い heart music
Passionate heart music
浴びたら spotlight
Once bathed in the spotlight
例えどんな嫌味も ごめん遊ばせ
No matter the sarcasm, please excuse me
wanna, wanna go, gonna, gonna go
no more time for goodbyes
ayy
eh-ehm, ah
最後までみてくれてありがとう☆彡
Thank you for watching to the very end! ☆彡
これからも私は私らしく、みんなと共にあります。
From now on, I'll continue to be true to myself, and stay by everyone's side.
新しい挑戦も続けて、まだ見ぬ世界を見に行こう！
Let's keep taking on new challenges and go see worlds we've never seen before!